prince3 = [
  {"question":"郷","Answer":"xiāng"},
  {"question":"突然","Answer":"tūrán"},
  {"question":"開朗","Answer":"kāilǎng"},
  {"question":"歇腳","Answer":"xiējiǎo"},
  {"question":"啟程","Answer":"qǐchéng"},
  {"question":"瀑布","Answer":"pùbù"},
  {"question":"時分","Answer":"shífēn"},
  {"question":"獅羣","Answer":"shīqún"},
  {"question":"閣樓","Answer":"gélóu"},
  {"question":"書桌","Answer":"shūzhuō"},
  {"question":"埋首","Answer":"máishǒu"},
  {"question":"壁爐","Answer":"bìlú"},
  {"question":"熄","Answer":"xī"},
  {"question":"繼","Answer":"jì"},
  {"question":"真誠","Answer":"zhēn chéng"},
  {"question":"再度","Answer":"zàidù"},
  {"question":"面臨","Answer":"miànlín"},
  {"question":"抉擇","Answer":"juézé"},
  {"question":"剩下","Answer":"shèngxià"},
  {"question":"印度","Answer":"yìndù"},
  {"question":"出產","Answer":"chūchǎn"},
  {"question":"劇本","Answer":"jùběn"},
  {"question":"萬萬不能","Answer":"wànwàn bùnéng"},
  {"question":"堅決地","Answer":"jiānjué dì"},
  {"question":"閣樓","Answer":"gélóu"},
  {"question":"簡陋","Answer":"jiǎnlòu"},
  {"question":"破","Answer":"pò"},
  {"question":"迅雷不及掩耳","Answer":"xùnléibùjíyǎněr"},
  {"question":"速度","Answer":"sùdù"},
  {"question":"聚精會神","Answer":"jùjīnghuì shén"},
  {"question":"揮動","Answer":"huīdòng"},
  {"question":"翅膀","Answer":"chìbǎng"},
  {"question":"珍貴","Answer":"zhēnguì"},
  {"question":"熱淚盈眶","Answer":"rèlèi yíngkuàng"},
  {"question":"盤旋","Answer":"pánxuán"},
  {"question":"船員","Answer":"chuányuán"},
  {"question":"拖上船","Answer":"tuō shàngchuán"},
  {"question":"嘿喲","Answer":"hēiyō"},
  {"question":"埃及","Answer":"āijí"},
  {"question":"繼續","Answer":"jìxù"},
  {"question":"映照","Answer":"yìngzhào"},
  {"question":"椰子樹","Answer":"yēzi shù"},
  {"question":"躺在","Answer":"tǎng zài"},
  {"question":"泥漿","Answer":"níjiāng"},
  {"question":"懶洋洋","Answer":"lǎn yángyáng"},
  {"question":"環顧四周","Answer":"huángù sìzhōu"},
  {"question":"彌補","Answer":"míbǔ"},
  {"question":"紅玫瑰","Answer":"hóng méigui"},
  {"question":"內心","Answer":"nèixīn"}
]